vipsetupservice.com 2013-12-07

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on  
the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to  
use the Internet's vast array of information, tools, and opportunities  
with complete confidence. 

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment  
to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our company  
collects information from all end users of our Internet services (the  
"Services")-those who access some of our Services but do not have  
accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who may purchase Products and/or  
pay a monthly service fee to subscribe to the Service ("Members")-what  
we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and  
Members have concerning the collection and use of such information. We  
request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

*Personal Information Our Company Collects and How It Is Used*

Introduction. Our company collects information in different ways from  
Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our Services and  
the network of Web sites accessible through our Service. We use this  
information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our  
Products and Services, and generally, do not share this information with  
third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected  
if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special  
circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required  
by law or other special cases described below. 

Registration: Members may be asked to provide certain personal  
information when they sign up for our Products or Services including  
name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit  
card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the  
Services. The personal information collected from Members during the  
registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as  
for billing purposes). This information is not shared with third  
parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances.

However, in instances where our company and a partner jointly promote  
our Services, we may provide the partner certain personal information,  
such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the  
Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of  
allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. 

In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner  
for any other purpose. We may also generate non-identifying and  
aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during  
registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members).  
As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and  
non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the  
Services. 

Our Company Partners and Sponsors: Some products and services may be  
offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with an affiliate,  
independent contractor seller or non-affiliated partner. To provide  
Visitors and Members some of these products and services, the partner  
may need to collect and maintain personal information. In these  
instances, you will be notified before any such data is collected or  
transferred and may decide not to use that particular service or feature. 

Additionally, our partners may have advertisements or co-branded Web  
Pages that are cosponsored by an affiliate, independent contractor  
seller, or non-affiliated partner. Our company may share non-identifying  
and aggregate information (except as described above), but not personal  
information, with such partners in order to administer the co-branded  
products or services offered. 

Online Shopping: At some Web sites, you can purchase products and  
services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog  
or new product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to  
provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address,  
phone number, and credit/debit card information. 

If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order  
sent directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information  
about the recipient, such as the recipient's name, address, and phone  
number. Our company has no control over the third parties' use of any  
personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please  
exercise care when doing so. 

If you order services or products directly from our company we will use  
the personal information you provide only to process that order. We do  
not share this information with outside parties except to the extent  
necessary to complete that order. 

Online Advertisements: Our company may display our online  
advertisements. In those cases we share aggregated and non-identifying  
information about our Visitors and Members collected through the  
registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions  
with these advertisers. 

Additionally, in some instances, we use this aggregated and  
non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements or joint  
ventures. For instance, an advertiser or joint venture company tells us  
the audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement  
tailored to the audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying  
information we have collected, we may then display or send the  
advertisement to the intended audience. Our company does not share  
personal information about its Visitors or Members with these  
advertisers or joint venture companies.

Responses to Email Inquiries: When Visitors or Members send email  
inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer the  
email inquiry we receive. Our company does not use the return email  
address for any other purpose and does not share the return email  
address with any third party. 

Voluntary Customer Surveys: We may periodically conduct both business  
and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to  
participate in these surveys because they provide us with important  
information that helps us to improve the types of products and services  
we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and  
responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is  
conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is  
voluntary. 

We may take the information we receive from individuals responding to  
our Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of  
other customers we may have, to create broader, generic responses to the  
survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education,  
employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then  
use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to  
you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated,  
non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

Special Cases: It is our company's policy not to use or share the  
personal information about Visitors of Members in ways unrelated to the  
ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt  
out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

However, we may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members,  
or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites  
accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole  
discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: credit  
agencies, collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law  
enforcement, or to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications  
Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental  
or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is  
necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone  
who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or Terms Of Service, or  
other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect our  
company and our Members. 

"Cookies" and How Our Company Uses Them. A "cookie" is a small data file  
that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites.  
Our company may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track  
information for statistical purposes to improve the products and  
services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. 

If you are a Visitor or Member we may use a cookie to save your settings  
and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do  
not enable third parties to access any of your customer information.  
Additionally, be aware that if you visit other Web sites where you are  
prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to  
accept cookies. 

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not  
control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for  
information collected through them. 

Our Company Commitment to Children's Privacy. Protecting children's  
privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with  
the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other  
applicable laws. Therefore we restrict our Web site to persons eighteen  
years or older.

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU  
ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS  
WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB  
SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILD  
ONLINE PRIVACY ACT (COPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO. 

Public Forums: Please remember that any information you may disclose in  
any Member Directory, or other public areas of our Web sites or the  
Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when  
deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas. 

Our Company's Commitment to Data Security: Services and Web sites we  
sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and  
alteration of the information under our control. While we make every  
effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems,  
we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party  
"hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. 

Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy: If you have any  
questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein,  
you may contact us through the contact information provided on this Web  
site. 

Revisions to This Policy: Our company reserves the right to revise,  
amend, or modify this policy, our Terms Of Service agreement, and our  
other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating  
this posting. Your use of this site after such changes are implemented  
constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of these changes. Please  
consult this privacy statement prior to every use for any changes.

Last updated: Aug 17, 2011
